boorah.com 2014-05-21

# Privacy

BooRah - Privacy Policy 

BooRah, an Intuit Company 

At Boorah, an Intuit Company, we place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. Our most important asset is our relationship with you. We want you to feel comfortable and confident when using our Web site.

We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Boorah web site, submitting in formation or using any of our products or services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?**

This Privacy Policy covers Boorah's treatment of personally identifiable information ("personal information") that we gather when you are accessing our web site and when you use our products or services. The types of per sonal information collected include your full name, address, and e-mail address. Also, this Policy covers our treatment of any personal information that our business partners share with us. This policy does not apply to t he practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our products and services. We collect the following types of information from our customers.

_Personal Information You Provide to Us:_

We may receive and store any information you enter on our web site or in connection with our products or services or that you provide to us in any other way. The personal informat ion you provide may be used for such purposes as customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about offers and new products and services.

_Personal Information Collected Automatically:_

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our web site or services. We may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested.  
Generally, our service may automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of users of our site and services and its components. We only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the web site or services so that we can improve those services. As part of this use of inform ation, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site and services. 

_E-mail Communications:_

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from us if your computer supports this type of program. We may also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary m essages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at mailing@Boorah.com and include sufficient information for us to identify your account. 

_What About Cookies?_

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site and on our service are visited and b y how many people. Our cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or to identify your name or e-mail add ress. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptan ce of each new cookie in a variety of ways. 

**WILL WE SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION ?**

Personal information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with your consent or as described below:

_Agents_ : We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have an y right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of personal information for the above purposes.  

_Business Transfers_ : If we, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, a nd that any acquirer of our may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.  

_Third Parties_ : We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Website, our employees, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.  

**IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?**

Your account personal information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to protect against unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your passwo rd appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?**

You may access some of your information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. The types of information that you can access and update will change as our web site changes. In general, you may update your account by emailing accounts@boorah.com and include sufficient information for us to identify your account. 

**WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?**

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information to us, even though it may be needed to receive services or take advantage of some of our offerings. 

You may be able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those that may be listed in the "What Personal Information Can I Access" section above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the u nrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your Boorah account by sending an e-mail to accounts@Boorah.com and responding affirmatively to any confirmation e-mails that we may send. Please note that some informatio n may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 

If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at mailing@boorah.com, and provide sufficient information for us to identify your account. Please note that if you do not want to receive leg al notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of our web site and services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

As explained earlier, the majority of browsers allow you to monitor and restrict our use of cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of some of our servic es or web site features. 

**EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 17, 2009. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, w e will notify you by posting an announcement on our web site. 

**QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy, please send us a detailed message to [info@boorah.com](mailto:privacy@boorah.com "email us").
